Riwayat Pemain Alter Ego 2017-2025
Kyzenn ()
Nama: The Mobile Legends: Bang Bang (MLBB) esports wiki covering everything from players, teams & transfers, to tournaments and results, heroes, equipment, & patches. | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: []
Arfy (Indonesia)
Nama: Arifudin Dingarai is an Indonesian player who is currently playing as a Gold Laner for Alter Ego. | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Gold Laner]
Hijumee (Indonesia)
Nama: Dalvin Putra | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Mid Laner]
Rinee (Indonesia)
Nama: Syahrul Ramadhan | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
DreamS (Indonesia)
Nama: Rachmad Wahyudi | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Roamer]
Nnael (Indonesia)
Nama: Manuel Simbolon | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
Owennn (Indonesia)
Nama: Alexander Owen | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Roamer]
Gebe (Indonesia)
Nama: Gilbert Goa | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
Aldo (Indonesia)
Nama: Ronaldo Lieberth (also known as Skipper) | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Coach]
R E K T (Indonesia)
Nama: Gustian | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Coach]
Haiz (Indonesia)
Nama: Dhannya Hoputra | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Gold Laner]
Tazz (Indonesia)
Nama: Darrel Wijaya | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Jungler, Mid Laner]
Cr1te (Indonesia)
Nama: Muhammad Yusuf (formerly known as 3yy) | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Mid Laner]
Munsters (Indonesia)
Nama: I Mahendra is an Indonesian player who is currently playing as an EXP Laner for ONIC Prodigy. | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [EXP Laner]
RoundeL ()
Nama:  | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: []
RaizeL ()
Variety (Indonesia)
Nama: Michael Tjandra | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
R E K T (Indonesia)
Nama: Gustian | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Coach]
Psychoo (Indonesia)
Nama: Teguh Firdaus | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: [Mid Laner, Roamer]
R a i z e L ()
Nama:  | Tanggal masuk Alter Ego: join no data | Roles: []