Riwayat Pemain Geek Fam ID 2017-2025
KennzyySkie ()
Nama:  | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: []
Maykids (Indonesia)
Nama: Muhammad Ardani is an Indonesian player who is currently playing as a Jungler for Geek Fam ID. | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
Veldora (Indonesia)
Nama: Kenley Zefanya | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [EXP Laner]
Mas4Ko (Indonesia)
Nama: Christian Wagiu | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Gold Laner]
Gobs ()
Nama:  | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: []
Vincentt (Indonesia)
Nama: Vincent Suwandhi | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
Hazle (Indonesia)
Nama: Muhammad Balakosa | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
Reyy (Indonesia)
Nama: Reynaldo Ferdiand | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
Nnael (Indonesia)
Nama: Manuel Simbolon | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
Markyyyyy (Philippines)
Nama: Mark Capacio | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Gold Laner]
Matt (Indonesia)
Nama: Matthew Geraldo | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Gold Laner, EXP Laner]
Aboy (Indonesia)
Nama: Valent Putra | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Mid Laner]
Renesmee (Indonesia)
Nama: Shaddam Evan is an Indonesian player who last played for Geek Fam ID Jr. | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Gold Laner]
Hadess (Philippines)
Nama: Jaymark Lazaro (also known as Janaaqt) | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Jungler]
Baloyskie (Philippines)
Nama: Allen Baloy (formerly known as Greed) | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Roamer]
RenV (Indonesia)
Nama: Rendy Kurniawan (formerly known as Ipin) | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [EXP Laner, Roamer]
Caderaa (Indonesia)
Nama: Mohammad Pambudi | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Gold Laner]
Lzuraa (Indonesia)
Nama: Muhammad Arif is an Indonesian player who last played for Geek Fam ID Jr. | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [Mid Laner]
Manskuy ()
Nama: The Mobile Legends: Bang Bang (MLBB) esports wiki covering everything from players, teams & transfers, to tournaments and results, heroes, equipment, & patches. | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: []
Schwann (Indonesia)
Nama: Bima Putra (also known as Adam) | Tanggal masuk Geek Fam ID: join no data | Roles: [EXP Laner, Gold Laner]